KaggleBot — AI-Powered Kaggle
Competition Strategy Agent
4-8 hours on competition discovery...
KaggleBot automates all of that
5-agent system built with Google ADK
Orchestrator → Scraper → Data → Strategy → Code
🔍 Scraper Agent: Titanic Competition
Metadata + Discussion Insights
📊 Data Agent: 100 rows × 12 columns
Quality: 89/100 | Target: Survived
📋 Strategy Agent: 3 Ranked Approaches
⏸️ HITL Gate — User Approves #1
💻 Code Agent: 170 Lines of Python
🔒 Security: safe = True
🔒 Three Layers of Security
Validation + Scanning + AST Analysis
📡 Full Pipeline Trace
5 Agents | 10 Tool Calls | 210ms
🧩 11 Concepts Demonstrated
6 Core + 5 Bonus
📊 43 Files | 5,239 Lines
5 Agents | 8 MCP Tools | 7/7 Tests
✅ All 7 E2E Tests Pass
Three Competitions Verified
Built with ❤️ using
Google ADK + Antigravity IDE